A Guide to the Records of the Policy Office of Governor Mark R. Warner, 2002-2006
Library of Virginia
- IV. Policy Analysts Files, 2002-2006 (accession 42409, 42410, 42412, 42421)., Extent: 25.20 cubic feet. (Box 175-246)
  - Subseries IV.A Robert M. Blue, Counselor to the Governor and Director of Policy,2002-2005 (accession 42410)., Extent: 7.35 cubic feet. (Box 175-195)
    - Attorney General
      - Fair Labor Standards Act, 2002 (Box 175, Folder 7)
      - Falwell Litigation, 2002 (Box 175, Folder 8)
      - Fees, 2002 (Box 175, Folder 8)
      - Governor/Attorney General Relations, 2003 (Box 175, Folder 8)
      - Intervention, 2002 (Box 175, Folder 8)
      - 2005 Legislative Agenda (Box 176, Folder 1)
      - 2002 Legislative Agenda (Box 176, Folder 1)
      - Meetings, 2002 (Box 176, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous, 2003 (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade
      - Department of Agriculture and Constituent Services, Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization, 2004 (Box 176, Folder 1)
      - Economic Crisis Strike Force, 2002 (Box 176, Folder 1)
      - Economic Development Partnership, 2002 (Box 176, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Employment Commission, Workforce Development, 2002-2003 (Box 176, Folder 1)
      - FOIA-General, 2002 (Box 176, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Housing Development Authority, Single Family Rule, 2002 (Box 176, Folder 1)
      - Department of Labor and Industry, Day of Rest (SB 659 (04)) (Box 176, Folder 1)
      - Department of Mines, Minerals and Energy, 2002-2004 (Box 176, Folder 1)
      - Public Utilities, 2002 (Box 176, Folder 2)
      - Secretary's Office, Smithfield, 2003 (Box 176, Folder 2)
      - Secretary's Office, Virginia Works, 2004 (Box 176, Folder 3)
      - Virginia Resources Authority, 2002 (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - Secretary of the Commonwealth
      - Allen and Gilmore Statements of Economic Interest (Box 176, Folder 4)
      - Appointments, General, 2003 (Box 176, Folder 5)
      - Appointments, Kay Slaughter, 2003 (Box 176, Folder 5)
      - Board of Medicine, 2002 (Box 176, Folder 5)
      - Conflicts of Interest Act (Box 176, Folder 5)
      - FOIA, Elizabeth Otte, 2002 (Box 176, Folder 5)
      - Make Women County, 2002 (Box 176, Folder 5)
      - Marrs Lawsuit, 2004-2005 (Box 176, Folder 5)
      - Melcher and Monroe, 2002 (Box 176, Folder 5)
      - Notaries, 2002 (Box 176, Folder 5)
      - Restoration of Rights (general), 2002 (part one) (Box 177, Folder 1)
      - Restoration of Rights (general), 2002 (part two) (Box 177, Folder 2)
      - Restoration of Rights (general), 2002 (part three) (Box 177, Folder 3)
      - Virginia Waste Management Board, Brad Pollack, 2002-2003 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Commonwealth Preparedness
      - BRAC, 2004 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Secretary of Education
      - Department of Education, Adequacy Litigation, 2003 (Box 177, Folder 4)
      - Department of Education, Charter Schools, 2002-2003 (Box 177, Folder 4)
      - Department of Education, Early Reading, 2002 (Box 177, Folder 5)
      - Department of Education, Education for a Lifetime, 2002-2005 (part one) (Box 178, Folder 1)
      - Department of Education, Education for a Lifetime, 2002-2005 (part two) (Box 178, Folder 2)
      - Department of Education, Education for a Lifetime, 2002-2005 (part three) (Box 178, Folder 3)
      - Department of Education, No Child Left Behind (NCLB), 2003 (Box 178, Folder 4)
      - Department of Education, Pre-Kindergarten, 2003 (Box 178, Folder 4)
      - Department of Education, Project Graduation, 2003 (Box 178, Folder 4)
      - Department of Education, School Choice, 2003 (Box 178, Folder 4)
      - Department of Education, Senior Year, 2003 (Box 178, Folder 5)
      - Department of Education, SERVE, 2003 (Box 179, Folder 1)
      - Department of Education, Standards of Learning, 2004 (Box 179, Folder 2)
      - Department of Education, Student Identifiers, 2002-2003 (Box 179, Folder 2)
      - Department of Education, Summer Reading, 2003 (Box 179, Folder 2)
      - Department of Education, Vouchers, 2002 (Box 179, Folder 2)
      - Gunston Hall (Box 179, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV), Appointments (Box 179, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV), Bond Campaign, 2002 (Box 179, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV), Commonwealth Scholars, 2002 (Box 179, Folder 2)
      - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV), Decentralization Initiatives, 2003-2005 (Box 179, Folder 3)
      - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV), Emergency Contraceptives, 2003 (Box 179, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV), General (Box 179, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV), Higher Education Funding, 2003 (Box 179, Folder 4)
      - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV), Higher Education Restructuring, 2005 (Box 179, Folder 4)
      - Secretary's Office, General Initiatives, 2003 (Box 179, Folder 4)
      - Secretary's Office, Higher Education Appointments, 2002 (Box 179, Folder 4)
      - Library of Virginia, General (Box 179, Folder 4)
      - Library of Virginia, Gilmore Papers, 2002 (Box 179, Folder 5)
      - Library of Virginia, Governor's Records, 2002 (Box 179, Folder 5)
      - Virginia Community College System (Box 180, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Military Institute, 2003 (Box 180, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 2002 (Box 180, Folder 1)
      - Williamsburg School, 2003-2004 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Secretary of Finance
      - Bond Issues, General, 2002 (Box 180, Folder 2)
      - Budget Reduction Plans, FOIA, Hardy, 2002 (Box 180, Folder 2)
      - Department of Planning and Budget, 2003 Budget Reduction Plans (part one) (Box 180, Folder 3)
      - Department of Planning and Budget, 2003 Budget Reduction Plans (part two) (Box 180, Folder 4)
      - Department of Planning and Budget, Budget and Tax Reform (2003 Kentucky Budget) (Box 180, Folder 5)
      - Department of Planning and Budget, Budget and Tax Reform (2003 Virginia Budget) (Box 180, Folder 6)
      - Department of Planning and Budget, Budget and Tax Reform, 2003-2004 (part one) (Box 181, Folder 1)
      - Department of Planning and Budget, Budget and Tax Reform, 2003-2004 (part two) (Box 181, Folder 2)
      - Department of Planning and Budget, Budget and Tax Reform, 2003-2004 (part three) (Box 181, Folder 3)
      - Department of Planning and Budget, Budget and Tax Reform, 2003-2004 (part four) (Box 181, Folder 4)
      - Department of Planning and Budget, Budget and Tax Reform, Governor's Vetoes of Items in Appropriation Bills, 1990-2002 (Box 181, Folder 5)
      - Department of Planning and Budget, Budget and Tax Reform, Legislative Budget Procedures (Box 182, Folder 1)
      - Department of Planning and Budget, Federal Grants, 2002 (Box 182, Folder 1)
      - Department of Planning and Budget, Line Item Veto, 2002-2003 (Box 182, Folder 1)
      - Department of Planning and Budget, National D-Day Memorial Investigation, 2002 (Box 182, Folder 2)
      - Department of Planning and Budget, Studies, 2003 (Box 182, Folder 2)
      - Secretary's Office, Fiscal Relief, 2003 (Box 182, Folder 2)
      - Secretary's Office, General, 2003-2004 (Box 182, Folder 2)
      - Secretary's Office, Tax Reform, 2003 (Box 182, Folder 3)
      - Department of Taxation, Estate Tax, 2003 (Box 182, Folder 3)
      - Department of Taxation, MSA, 2003 (Box 182, Folder 3)
      - Department of Taxation, Sales Tax Exemptions, HB 5002 (04) Special Session (Box 182, Folder 4)
      - Department of Taxation, Tax Reform, 2003-2004 (Box 182, Folder 5)
      - Department of Treasury, Escheat, 2004 (Box 182, Folder 5)
      - Department of Treasury, Virginia Public School Authority, 2004 (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - Governor's Office
      - Archiving (Box 183, Folder 1)
      - Bill Review, General (Box 183, Folder 1)
      - Cabinet Confirmation, 2002 (Box 183, Folder 1)
      - Civil Rights Statute (Box 183, Folder 1)
      - Coalition for Virginia's Future, 2003 (Box 183, Folder 1)
      - Commonwealth Preparedness, 2002 (Box 183, Folder 1)
      - Constituent Services, Falun Gong, 2002 (Box 183, Folder 1)
      - Statements of Economic Interest (Governor Warner), 2002-2005 (Box 183, Folder 2)
      - Ethics Other States (Box 183, Folder 3)
      - Ethics Package (Box 183, Folder 4)
      - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 2002 (Box 183, Folder 5)
      - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA), 2003 (Box 183, Folder 5)
      - FOIA, Orris Avent, 2002 (Box 183, Folder 5)
      - FOIA, Roger Christman, 2002 (Box 183, Folder 5)
      - FOIA, Brett A. Feinstein, 2002 (Box 183, Folder 5)
      - FOIA, Thomas Gasparoli, 2004 (Box 183, Folder 5)
      - FOIA, Christopher R. Hedrick, 2002 (Box 183, Folder 5)
      - FOIA, Byron P. Kloeppel, 2005 (Box 183, Folder 5)
      - FOIA, Hugh Lessig, 2003 (Box 183, Folder 5)
      - FOIA, Bob Lewis (AP), 2002 (Box 183, Folder 5)
      - FOIA, Steven N. Lisson, 2004-2005 (Box 183, Folder 5)
      - FOIA, Paula E. Nickens, 2002 (Box 183, Folder 5)
      - FOIA, George Randolf, 2002 (Box 183, Folder 6)
      - FOIA, Robert S. Schwartz, 2002 (Box 183, Folder 6)
      - FOIA, Mike Shear (Washington Post), 2003 (Box 183, Folder 6)
      - General Processes (Box 183, Folder 6)
      - Judicial Appointments, General, 2002-2003 (Box 183, Folder 6)
      - Judicial Appointments 2005 Session (Box 183, Folder 6)
      - Judicial Appointments, Alexandria Circuit Court (18th Circuit), 2003-2005 (part one) (Box 184, Folder 1)
      - Judicial Appointments, Alexandria Circuit Court (18th Circuit), 2003-2005 (part two) (Box 184, Folder 2)
      - Judicial Appointments, Court of Appeals, 2002 (part one) (Box 184, Folder 3)
      - Judicial Appointments, Court of Appeals, 2002 (part two) (Box 184, Folder 4)
      - Judicial Appointments, Court of Appeals, 2002 (part three) (Box 184, Folder 5)
      - Judicial Appointments, Court of Appeals, D. Arthur Kelsey, 2002 (part one) (Box 185, Folder 1)
      - Judicial Appointments, Court of Appeals, D. Arthur Kelsey, 2002 (part two) (Box 185, Folder 2)
      - Judicial Appointments, Arlington Circuit Court (17th Circuit), 2003 (Box 185, Folder 3)
      - Judicial Appointments, Bath County (25th Circuit), 2003 (Box 185, Folder 3)
      - Judicial Appointments, Fairfax Circuit Court (19th Circuit), 2002 (Box 185, Folder 4)
      - Judicial Appointments, Hampton Circuit Court (8th Circuit), 2004-2005 (Box 185, Folder 5)
      - Judicial Appointments, Richmond Circuit Court (13th Circuit), Correspondence, 2002 (Box 185, Folder 6)
      - Judicial Appointments, Richmond Circuit Court (13th Circuit), Resumes, 2002 (Box 186, Folder 1)
      - Judicial Appointments, Suffolk Circuit Court (5th Circuit), 2002-2003 (Box 186, Folder 2)
      - Judicial Appointments, Suffolk Circuit Court (5th Circuit), 2002-2003 (Box 186, Folder 2)
      - Judicial Appointments, 2003 Session (Box 186, Folder 3)
      - Judicial Appointments, 2002 Session (Box 186, Folder 4)
      - Judicial Inquiry and Review Commission, 2002-2003 (Box 186, Folder 4)
      - Line of Succession (Box 186, Folder 5)
      - Litigation, Mark Staunton Beatty v. Mark R. Warner, 2004 (Box 186, Folder 5)
      - Litigation, Yi-Jer Huang et al. v. Jerry Kilgore and Mark Warner, 2002-2003 (Box 186, Folder 6)
      - Litigation, Robert G. Marshall, et al. v. Mark R. Warner, et al., 2004 Budget (part one) (Box 187, Folder 1)
      - Litigation, Robert G. Marshall, et al. v. Mark R. Warner, et al., 2004 Budget (part two) (Box 187, Folder 2)
      - Litigation, Robert G. Marshall, et al. v. Mark R. Warner, et al., 2004 Budget (part three) (Box 187, Folder 3)
      - Litigation, Michael Sindram v. S. Randolph Sengel, Dietra Y. Trent, Mark R. Warner, 2005 (Box 187, Folder 4)
      - Litigation, Williams v. Warner, et al., 2003 (Box 187, Folder 4)
      - Mansion (Box 187, Folder 4)
      - Mary Linda Mann Case, 2002 (Box 187, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 187, Folder 5)
      - North Carolina Meeting, 2002 (Box 187, Folder 6)
      - National Governor's Association (NGA), General, 2002-2004 (Box 187, Folder 6)
      - Olundar Ogunde Case, 2002 (Box 187, Folder 7)
      - Press Office, Appalachian Law School, 2002 (Box 188, Folder 1)
      - Records Retention, 2002 (Box 188, Folder 1)
      - Two-Term Limit for Governor, 2004 (Box 188, Folder 1)
      - Travel Regulations (Box 188, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Executive Institute (VEI), 2003 (Box 188, Folder 1)
      - Workplace Harassment Policy, 2002 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Secretary of Health and Human Resources
      - Department of Health, Birth-Related Neurological Injury Compensation Program, 2002 (Box 188, Folder 2)
      - Department of Health, Flu Vaccine, 2004 (Box 188, Folder 2)
      - Council on Indians, Federal Recognition, 2003 (Box 188, Folder 2)
      - Department of Medical Assistance Services, Medicaid Reform, 2005 (Box 188, Folder 2)
      - Department of Medical Assistance Services, Prescription Drugs, 2003 (Box 188, Folder 2)
      - Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services (DMHMRSAS), Eugenics, 2002 (Box 188, Folder 2)
      - DMHMRSAS, Mental Health Restructuring, 2002 (Box 188, Folder 2)
      - DMHMRSAS, Sexually Violent Predators, 2002-2003 (Box 188, Folder 3)
      - Secretary's Office, Healthy Virginians, 2004 (Box 188, Folder 4)
      - Secretary's Office, Partial Birth Abortion, 2002 (part one) (Box 188, Folder 5)
      - Secretary's Office, Partial Birth Abortion, 2002 (part two) (Box 189, Folder 1)
      - Secretary's Office, Partial Birth Abortion, 2002 (part three) (Box 189, Folder 2)
      - Department of Social Services, Assisted Living Facilities (Box 189, Folder 3)
      - Department of Social Services, Birth Certificates, 2002 (Box 189, Folder 3)
      - Department of Social Services, Faith Based Initiatives, 2002 (Box 189, Folder 3)
      - Department of Social Services, TANF/VIEW, 2003 (Box 189, Folder 4)
      - Virginia Health Care Foundation, 2002 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Homeland Security
      - General, 2002 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Independent Agencies
      - State Corporation Commission (SCC), Energy Deregulation, 2003 (Box 189, Folder 6)
      - State Corporation Commission (SCC), Bureau of Insurance, 2002 (Box 189, Folder 7)
      - State Corporation Commission (SCC), Tenaska, 2002 (Box 189, Folder 7)
      - Office for Protection and Advocacy, 2003 (part one) (Box 190, Folder 1)
      - Office for Protection and Advocacy, 2003 (part two) (Box 190, Folder 2)
      - Virginia Retirement System, Actuarial Assumptions, 2002 (Box 190, Folder 3)
      - Workers' Compensation Commission, 2002 (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Judicial
      - Public Defender Commission, 2002-2004 (Box 190, Folder 4)
      - Virginia State Bar, Corporate Counsel, 2002 (Box 190, Folder 5)
      - Virginia Supreme Court, 2003-2004 (Box 190, Folder 5)
      - Virginia Supreme Court, 21 Day Rule, 2002-2003 (Box 190, Folder 6)
      - Virginia Supreme Court, Judicial Performance Study (Box 191, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Supreme Court, Judicial Selection Reform, 2003 (Box 191, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Supreme Court, Law Clerks, 2004 (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - Legislature
      - Crime Commission, 2003-2004 (Box 191, Folder 2)
      - Redistricting, 2002-2004 (Box 191, Folder 3)
      - Research Germaneness (Box 191, Folder 4)
      - Veto Cases (Box 191, Folder 5)
      - Procedural Issues, 2004 Session (Box 191, Folder 6)
      - Abortion, 2003 Session (part one) (Box 191, Folder 7)
      - bortion, 2003 Session (part two) (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Secretary of Natural Resources
      - Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance Department, 2002 (Box 192, Folder 2)
      - Department of Conservation and Recreation, Concealed Weapons, 2002 (Box 192, Folder 2)
      - Department of Conservation and Recreation, Occonechee, 2003-2004 (Box 192, Folder 2)
      - Department of Environmental Quality, Battle Creek Landfill, 2003 (Box 192, Folder 2)
      - Department of Environmental Quality, Campbell County Landfill, 2003 (Box 192, Folder 2)
      - Department of Environmental Quality, Chesapeake Bay Nutrient Reductions, 2004 (Box 192, Folder 2)
      - Department of Environmental Quality, Crutchfield v. State Water Control Board, 2002 (Box 192, Folder 3)
      - Department of Environmental Quality, Drought, 2002 (Box 192, Folder 4)
      - Department of Environmental Quality, Mirant, 2003 (Box 192, Folder 5)
      - Department of Environmental Quality, New Source Review, 2003 (Box 192, Folder 6)
      - Department of Environmental Quality, Nutrient Reductions, 2003 (Box 192, Folder 7)
      - Department of Environmental Quality, Richmond, SIP Litigation, 2002-2003 (Box 192, Folder 8)
      - Department of Environmental Quality, Shenandoah National Park, 2004 (Box 192, Folder 9)
      - Department of Environmental Quality, Standing, 2002 (Box 192, Folder 10)
      - Department of Environmental Quality, Virginia v. Maryland, 2002 (Box 193, Folder 1)
      - Department of Environmental Quality, Wetlands, 2003 (Box 193, Folder 2)
      - James River Ghost Fleet, 2002 (Box 193, Folder 2)
      - Secretary's Office, Widewater, 2003 (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - Secretary of Public Safety
      - Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control, Bolick v. Roberts, 2002 (Box 193, Folder 4)
      - Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control, Regulatory Review, 2004 (Box 193, Folder 5)
      - Commonwealth's Attorneys' Services Council, 2002 (Box 193, Folder 5)
      - Department of Criminal Justice Services, Crime in Minority Communities, 2003 (Box 193, Folder 5)
      - Department of Criminal Justice Services, Drug Courts, 2002-2004 (Box 193, Folder 5)
      - Department of Criminal Justice Services, Violence Against Women Act - Grants, 2002 (Box 194, Folder 1)
      - Department of Corrections, Chesapeake Parole Office, 2003 (Box 194, Folder 2)
      - Department of Corrections, Corrections Facilities Task Force, 2002 (Box 194, Folder 2)
      - Department of Corrections, Offender Forecasts, 2003 (Box 194, Folder 2)
      - Department of Corrections, Virginia Beach Jail, 2002 (Box 194, Folder 2)
      - Executions, Atkins Subcommittee, Virginia State Crime Commission, 2002 (Box 194, Folder 3)
      - Firearms, 2002 (Box 194, Folder 4)
      - FOIA, Bill Baskerville, 2002 (Box 194, Folder 4)
      - Department of Juvenile Justice, 2003 (Box 194, Folder 4)
      - Parole Board, 2002 (Box 194, Folder 4)
      - Virginia State Police, CapWIN (Capital Wireless Integrated Network Compact), 2004 (Box 194, Folder 4)
      - Virginia State Police, Matricardi Investigation, 2002 (Box 194, Folder 4)
      - Virginia State Police, Primary Seat Belt (Box 194, Folder 4)
      - Virginia State Police, Special State Police Officers, 2004 (Box 194, Folder 4)
      - STARS, 2004 (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - Secretary of Technology
      - (Box 194, Folder 5)
      - (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - Secretary of Transportation
      - Department of Motor Vehicles, Hybrids, 2004 (Box 194, Folder 6)
      - Department of Motor Vehicles, Immigration Issues, 2002 (Box 194, Folder 6)
      - Department of Motor Vehicles, Legal Presence, 2003 (Box 194, Folder 6)
      - Department of Motor Vehicles, Office Closures, 2003 (Box 194, Folder 6)
      - Department of Motor Vehicles, Sons of Confederate Veterans, 2002 (Box 194, Folder 7)
      - VDOT, FOIA, Washington Post, 2002 (Box 195, Folder 1)
      - VDOT, Hybrids, 2004 (Box 195, Folder 2)
      - VDOT, HOV Lanes, 2004 (Box 195, Folder 2)
      - VDOT, Route 58, 2002 (Box 195, Folder 2)
      - VDOT, Sales Tax Referenda, 2002 (Box 195, Folder 3)
      - VDOT, Sierra Club v. EPA, 2002 (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Liaison Office
      - FCC, 2002-2003 (Box 195, Folder 5)
  - Subseris IV.B. Williams L. Murray, Deputy Director of Policy,2002-2005 (accession 42421)., Extent: 1.05 cubic feet. (Box 196-198)
    This subseries is housed in 3 boxes and is arranged alphabetically by subject. Murray served as Deputy Director of Policy and Deputy Secretary of Health and Human Resources from 2002 until July 2003. Murray was the Governor's health-care expert. He also developed the state's water use restrictions during the 2002 drought. He returned to the Warner Administration in 2004 and remained for the remainder of the administration.
    Notable documents related to the 2002 drought include: copies of correspondence from Governor Warner to U.S. Secretary of Agriculture Ann Veneman asking her to declare numerous Virginia localities agricultural disaster areas; copies of USDA Emergency Designation Requests which include Disaster Assessment Reports; and daily drought updates from September to November 2002.
    - Secretary of Administration, 2004-2005 (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - 2005 Agency Bills (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - American Hospital Association, Talking Points for Governor Warner, 2 May 2005 (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Administrative Process Act (APA) Work Group, nd (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - BRAC Commission, Testimony of Governor Mark R. Warner, 20 August 2005 (Box 196, Folder 4a)
    - Drought, 2002 (part one) (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - Drought, 2002 (part two) (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - Drought, 2002 (part three) (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - Drought, 2002 (part four) (Box 196, Folder 8)
    - Drought, 2002 (part five) (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Drought, 2005 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Energy - Energy Policy, 2005 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Energy - Hardy Project (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Energy - Hybrid Fuel Systems, 2005 (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - eVA Financing. 2005 (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - Executive Orders, Drafts, 2003-2005 (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Health Care - American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists Materials, 2004 (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - Health Care - Child Fatality Review Team, 2005 (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - Health Care - Children's Mental Health (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - Health Care - Community Health Centers, 2004 (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - Health Care - Health Care Reading, 2005 (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - Health Care - Medicaid Reforms, 2005 (Box 197, Folder 13)
    - Health Care - Mental Health Capital Expenditures, 2005 (Box 197, Folder 14)
    - Health Care - Sentara Certificate of Public Need, 2004 (Box 197, Folder 15)
    - Health Care - United Health Talk (Dr. Tuckson), 17 July 2005 (Box 197, Folder 16)
    - Health Care - Virginia Commonwealth University Health System, 2004 (Box 197, Folder 17)
    - Higher Education - Charter Universities, 2004 (part one) (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Higher Education - Charter Universities, 2004 (part two) (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Higher Education - Higher Education, 2004 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Medicaid Provider Rates, 2004 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - National Governors Association, 2004 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Olmstead Initiative, 2004 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Organ Donation, 2004 (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - Southern Governors' Association, 2004 (Box 198, Folder 8)
  - Subseries IV.C. David H. Hallock, Assistant to the Governor for Policy and Deputy Counselor,2002-2004 (accession 42409)., Extent: 7.45 cubic feet. (Box 199-219)
    This subseries is housed in 21 boxes and is arranged alphabetically by subject. Hallock's areas of expertise were health care, natural resources, finance, public safety and transportation. His files contain records related to a wide range of topics including health care, minority procurement, higher education, redistricting, drought and various transportation issues including I-81, Dulles Rail Project, DMV closings and the Aviation World's Fair of 2003. Hallock worked for Governor Warner from 2002 until August 2004.